National Tots and Teens, Inc., DC Chapter 138 138
Stage
National Tots and Teens, Inc., DC Chapter Records
1953-2001
Stage
138
11 cubic feet; 11 boxes
The DC chapter of National Tots and Teens, Inc. was organized in June 1959 when thirteen mothers gathered to create a local chapter in the District. As a national organization,Tots and Teens, Inc. served to offer recreational, social and cultural development to children and establish an understanding of the relationship between parent and child. The DC chapter of Tots and Teens, Inc. records document the organization's operations and includes agendas, by-laws, event flyers, family rosters, meeting minutes, memorabilia, news bulletins, newsletters, and other items.
Custodial History
Doreen Hope, a member of the DC chapter of National Tots and Teens, Inc., donated this collection to the DC Public Library's Special Collections department.
Biographical / Historical
National Tots and Teens, Inc. was founded in Los Angeles in1954 when Geraldine Jacoway Ross desired a way for whole families to interact with each other as well and develop relationships with local families. The organization served to offer recreational, social and cultural development to children and establish an understanding of the relationship between parent and child. Members believed that the family should operate as whole unit, and the goal was to reach each member of the family by involving everyone in all program activities regardless of age. At the time, National Tots and Teens, Inc. was divided into four regions: Eastern Seaboard, Midwest, Central and Far West. The DC chapter of National Tots and Teens, Inc. frequently interacted with the Cleveland (Ohio) and St. Louis (Missouri) chapters.Organized in June 1959 when thirteen mothers gathered to create a local chapter. Mrs. Carolyn B. Buford was instrumental in creating the DC chapter. By 1962, membership had grown to 60 families with about 115 children. Members hosted theater events, went on ski trips, developed a bowling league, and established an annual tennis league. The chapter was also involved in community service/volunteers projects in the area at the Junior Village, the Merriweather Home for Children, Children's Hospital and the Uplift House for Children. The chapter was also involved with the National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP), holding a full lifetime membership.
Scope and Contents
The DC chapter of Tots and Teens, Inc. records document theorganization's operations and includes agendas, by-laws, event flyers, family rosters, meeting minutes, memorabilia, news bulletins, newsletters, and other items.
- Series 1
  - Graduate Dance Programs, 1966-1973 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Graduate Dance programs, 1974-1979 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Graduate Dance Programs, 1980-1990 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Tots and Teens DC Stationary, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Tots Making Easter Baskets Newspaper Article, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Tots and Teens Third Triennial Convention Correspondence, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Tots and Teens News: A Salute to Our Graduates, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Tots and Teens Reunion Planning Committee, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Catoctin Mountain Area Event Info, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Name and Address List, undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Family Conference Request List, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - African American News Volume VI No. 2 Spring/Summer 1995 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - DC Club Rosters, 1962-1963 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Tentative Group Activities Grid, undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - D.C Chapter Minutes of Regular Meeting, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Table Manners and Etiquette Notes, undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Suggested Amendments to the By-Laws of D.C Tots and Teens, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Agenda for Meeting, 1966-09-19 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Tots and Teens Newsletter September Issue 1996, 1996-09 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - DC Tots and Teens News Bulletin, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - National Tots and Teens 50th Anniversary Celebration, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Luncheon and Founders Day Program, 1969-1995 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Organization Constitution, undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - T and T Associate Members List, undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - By Laws of the Tots and Teens, undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Family Roster D.C Chapter, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Family Roster DC Chapter, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Family Roster DC Chapter, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - DC Tots and Teens Officer List, undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Tots and Teens Officer List, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Teen Group Roster, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Atlantic City Bus Schedule, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - 1st Annual Fine Arts Fair Info, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Patriot Cruise Booking Confirmation Lunch and Dinner Menu, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Suggested Items for Christmas Baskets, undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - T and T Associates Birthday List, undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Agenda, 1991-01-18 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Meeting Agenda, 1991-01-16 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Constitution and By-Laws, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Agenda, 1987-01-16 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Agenda, 1990-10-06 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - 1988-1989 Groups and Business Meeting Dates (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Minutes of Executive Board Meeting, 1991-03-11 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - 20th Anniversary Celebration Invitation and Meeting Notes, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - T and T Associates Founding Correspondence, undated (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Announcement, 1988-01-15 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Minutes of the Membership, 1991-03-15 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Telephone Hotline info, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Proposed Budget 1990-1991 Club Year (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - T and T Associates Proposed Budget, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - T and T Associates Newsletter, 1990-09 - 1990-10 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - T and T Associates Newsletter, 1991-03 - 1991-04 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - T and T Associates Newsbreak, 1980-01 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - T and T Associates Newsletter, 1990-03 - 1990-04 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - T and T Associates Newsbreak, 1985-12 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - T and T Associates Newsbreak, 1988-08 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Regional Council Meeting Order of Business List, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - 1969 Convention Info (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Holiday Inn Brochures, undated (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Organization History, undated (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Board Meeting May 8, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - 1966-1967 Committee Chairman (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Agenda for Meeting, 1996-09-19 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Agenda, 1966-09-12 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Second Triennial National Convention, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Preamble/Aims/Motto/Code Ethnics etc., undated (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Ball Committee June 16th, undated (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Scrap notes/Calculations, undated (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Tots and Teens Family Luncheon 1967 Info (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - List of those who paid in full, undated (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Letitia Randall Correspondence, 1960-1962 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - First National Conference Financial Report, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Group Activities Assignments, 1962-1963 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Tots and Teens Inc News Bulletin, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Tots and Teens Newsletter, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Washington Charter Hostess Roster, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Second Triennial National Convention Agenda, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Annual Luncheon Agenda, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - 12-14 Group Minutes, undated (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Executive Board Meeting Monday, 1966-11-14 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Tots and Teens Newsletter, 1966-11 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Meeting Agenda, 1967-01-16 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Meeting Agenda, 1967-03-20 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Tots and Teens Newsletter, 1967-01 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Call Meeting Agenda, 1967-04-17 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Tots and Teens Newsletter, 1967-03 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - February 20, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Meeting Agenda, 1966-11-21 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Puppet Show List, undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Duties of Officers, undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Suggeted Amendments to the By Laws, undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Suggested Field Trips, undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Constitution Committee 3rd Triennial National Convention, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - 1971 Committee Report (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - 1964 New Years Eve Party Invitation (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Casual Classics Club 35th Anniversary Invitation, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - 14th Anniversary Meeting, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - 25th Anniversary Celebration Souvenir Program Advertising Contract, undated (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Autumn Fling Invitation, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Definition of a Grandmother, undated (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Adult Game Night Flyer, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Pre Christmas Ball Parent Invitation, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Thank you card to Eveyln, undated (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - "The Explosive 60" presented by Tots and Teens Inc., 1970 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Group and Committee Chairman, undated (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Position List, undated (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Nominating Committee Report, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Tots and Teens "What in a name" Crossword Puzzle, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Officer List, 1968-1975 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Concern Correspondence, undated (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Group VI One Day Pckage Correspondence, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Tots and Teens Tidbits Vol. 2 No. 2, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - A Virginia Experience 12-14 Group Retreat Info, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - "Rappin Bout the Whole Thing", 1972 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - TNT Teen Travel Clu Flyer, undated (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Founders Day Observance Program Info, undated (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - "Are you Active" Poem, undated (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Tots and Teens Tidbits Vol. 1 No. 6, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Lift Every Voice Lyrics, undated (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Membership Info, undated (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - National TNT Newsletter, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Teen Membership Correspondence, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Teen Ball Report Correspondence, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Tots and Teens Tidbits Vol. 1, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Train Itinerary to Kings Dominion, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - National TNT Newsletter, 1977-01 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Teen Weekend Retreat Info, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Teen Ball Info, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Tots and Teens Minutes, 1979-01-15 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Tots and Teens Tidbits Vol. 1, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Tots and Teens Tidbits Vol. 1 No. 4 and 5, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Regional/State Activities, undated (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - The National TNT Youth Officers, undated (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Editors Corner and Note from the President, undated (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Evelyn Horad's Social the Washington Afro-American Post, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - History of Activities, undated (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - "Black Organizations Goal is Political Activism" The Evening Sun Article, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Roster of Membership, undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Black Nativity at the Kennedy Center Info, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - "As We Knew Caroln B. Buford", undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - "Money for Meriweather Home for Orphan Children"/Washington Afro American, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - The Pink Siamese Program, undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - "Women's View" Afro-American Newspaper Article, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Roster of Membership 1984-1984, undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Outstanding Tots and Teens Service Award, undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Bowling Tournament Info, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Group Activities for 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Teen Parent Correspondence, undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Newspaper Article, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Report of Program Committee, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Letitia Randall Correspondence, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Tots and Teens Family News, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Homecoming Info, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Group Activities 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - TNT Bowling League Info, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - "Rappin Bout the Whole Thing", undated (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Florida's WeekiWachee Brochure, undated (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - History/Goals/Prayer, undated (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Organizational Structure, undated (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Basic Operations, undated (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Services Performed, undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Other information and Family Roster, undated (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Teen Ball Photo Album, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Photo Album, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Certificate of Incorporation, undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Thank you correspondence, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Tots and Teens Tidbits Vol. 3 No. 5, undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - "A Boogie Down" Newspaper Article, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - The Plymouth Prompter Vol. 27 No. 1, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Appreciation Correspondence, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - James Hubert "Eubie" Blake, undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Round House Theatre's Mostly Music and More Pamphlet, undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Why I Want to Go to Romania, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Tots and Teens Newsletter, 1967-03 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Prayer and Songs, undated (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - American Heritage Day Presentation Notes, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Graduate Honors Invitation, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Tots and Teens Tidbits Vol. 1 No. 7, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Founders Day Program, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - National TNT Newsletter, 1973-12 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Song Lyrics, undated (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Tots and Teens News, 1971-03 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Certificate for Outstanding Service, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Theory of Assertive Training Points, undated (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Carolyn Buford - Years of Service as President 1959-1961, undated (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Youth Workbook for Nation Youth Assembly, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Youth Organizational Chart, undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - DC Tots and Teens News Bulletin 1962 and 1963 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - National Newsletter Vol. I, 1962-10 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - T and T Associates Membership, 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Tots and Teens Club 1962-1963 Mother/Children Roster (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - 1960-1961 Roster Tots and Teens (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - 1965-1966 Season Committee Chairman (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Group Chairman and Co-Chairman 1962-1963 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Chairman Correspondence, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - DC Tots and Teens Officers for 1962-1963 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Tots "N" Teens 6-8 Group 1962-1963 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Costumes for Bye Bye Burdie, undated (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Social Graces, undated (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Treasures Report 1959-1960, undated (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - DC. Tots and Teens 1961-1962 Season (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - National Newsletter Vol. I, 1962-10 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - DC Tots and Teens Bulletin May 1959-1965 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Tour to San Francisco and Los Angeles California, 1972-08 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - United Airlines Stationary, undated (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Hotel Drak Wiltshire and San Francisco photographs, undated (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Performing Arts Godspell: American Conservatory Theatre Magazine, undated (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Map of Sequoia and Kings Canyon, undated (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Grand Canyon Info, undated (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - "On the Strip" las Vegas Nevada Bus Transfer and Post Card, undated (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Universal City Tour Information, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Story of Each Place Visited, undated (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Disney Land Info, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Hoover Dam Trip Info, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Triennial Convention Programs/Agendas, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Tots and Teens Handbook, undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Fourth Triennial National Convention, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Chapter Reports National Convention, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Sixth Triennial National Convention, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - 10th National Convention, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - National Newsletter, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - National Convention, 1969-08 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Midwest Region, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - 5th Triennial National Convention August 1975, 1975-08 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - 1976 National Executive Board Meeting (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - 1977 National Executive Board (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Eastern Seaboard Regional Family Conference, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Mid-Day Club of Cleveland, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - T and T Newsbreak April, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Expression of love and Affection Correspondence, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - TNT News Blurps, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Tots and Teens News, 1971-03 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Midwest Region, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Tots and Teens Inc. Program Committee Report, 1966-08-10 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - T and T Associates Christmas Party, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - June 1993 Installation of Officers Photographs, 1993-06 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - T and T Associates Newsletter, 1991-11 - 1991-12 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Minutes of the Membership Meeting, 1992-01-17 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - T and T Newsletter, 1990-06 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - T and T Associates Newsletter, 1990-09 - 1990-10 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Member Correspondence, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - T and T Associates Newsletter, 1991-11 - 1991-12 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Meeting Info, 1992-2005 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - 1992 Music Man Flyer (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - T and T Associates Newsletter March- April 1990-1993 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Christmas Gathering Correspondence, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Newsbreak Vol. 5, 1988-05 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Minutes of the Membership Meeting, 1991-11-15 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Minutes of Membership Meeting, 1991-05-17 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Minutes of the Membership Meeting, 1991-09-21 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Congratulations Correspondence, undated (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Park Office Map, undated (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Charges and Rules for Hall Rentals for Drivers Chauffeurs, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Facilities Reservation Application and Use Agreement, undated (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - T and T Associates Meeting Notice, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Group Assignment, undated (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - St. Michael's Maryland Trip Info, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Change in By Laws and Constitution Notice, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - 20th Anniversary Celebration invitation, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - T and T Associates Happy New Year Flyer, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Proposed Budget 1990-1991 Club Year (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - 1991 Trip to Atlantic City Flyer (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - 1991 Activities Calendar (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - President's Message, undated (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Member Roster, undated (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Constitution Committee Report, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - T and T Associates Newsletter, 1992-11 - 1992-12 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - 1993 Associates Correspondence (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - T and T Associates Newsletter, 1992-09 - 1992-10 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Thanksgiving At Sea Carnival Festival Info, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - T and T Associates Newsletter, 1992-11 - 1992-12 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - For All Those Born Prior to 1945, undated (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Seminar Series: Multiculturalism and Anti-Racism, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Handwritten Notes, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Committee Report, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Treasures Report 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Official Forms, undated (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - National Tots and Teens, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Agenda, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Dues Paid, 1979-1981 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Meeting Correspondence and Planning Meeting Notes, 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - 1992 Newsletters (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - 1992 Meeting Minutes (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - January-February 1993 Newsletter (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Member Rosters, 1979-1993 (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Reader's Digest, undated (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - St. Michael's Trip Invitation, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Name Change on Checking Account Correspondence, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Merry Christmas Correspondence, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Handbook Revision Committee Recommendations, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Member Correspondence, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Treasure's Report, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - T and T Associates Account Info and Balance, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Stationary, undated (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - T and T Associates Newsbreak Vol 1 No. 3 and 4, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Group Lunch Menu: Salty Oyster Restaurants and Seafood Market, undated (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - St. Michael's Maryland Trip, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Function Prospectus, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Officer List, 1998-1999 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Treasure's Court, 1998-1999 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Group Sales Contract for Raisin in the Sun, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Press Room Reservation, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Associate Meeting Correspondence, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Due Request, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Holiday Calendar, undated (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Jane Tyler Correspondence, 1996-1999 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - 1998 Graduation Family Celebration Invitation (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Rock Creek Park Map, undated (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Handwritten Notes, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Special Services Info, undated (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Facilities Rental Contract for Resin in the Sun, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Treasury Reports and Services and Facilities Contracts, 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - All First: T and T Associates Relationship with Interest, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Wheaton Regional Park Permit Request Form, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - T and T Associates Check, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Membership Roster and Officers, 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Receipts and Secretary Report 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Hotel Greeters Guide, 1962-06-28 - 1962-07-05 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Regional Correspondence, 1959-1960 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Children's Books on the Negro History List, undated (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Eastern Seaboard Youth Group Newsletter December, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Tots and Teens Report Second Annual Regional Conference, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Second Annual Conference, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Handwritten Notes and Calculations, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - First Annual One Day Conference, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Expense Documents, 1963-1967 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Notes on National Historian and Recommendation from Financial Secretary and Regional Council, 1964-1965 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Memo from the President's Desk, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Regional Council Handbook, undated (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Convention Luncheon Pamphlet, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - 1979 Newsletter (National) (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - National Constitutional, undated (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Endorsement of Wilma Fairley for Second National Vice President, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Youth Meeting, 1972-08 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - August 1971/72 Board Meeting Memo (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Youth Organization Chart, undated (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - By Laws of Eastern Seaboard Region Youth Group, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - National Youth Committee Notes and Rules of National Youth Assembly, undated (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - By Laws, undated (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Constitution Committee Report - 3rd Triennial Convention, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - National Convention - Minutes/Agendas/Correspondence, 1971-1979 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - National Convention - Agenda/Recommendations/Reports, 1963-1997 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Regional Conference Payment Reciepts, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - National Convention Flyers Committee Reports and Correspondence, 1962-1966 (Box 11, Folder 4)